Inventory of the Papers of Judge George H. Revercomb, 1971-1993
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Law Library
Papers of Judge George H. Revercomb, 1971-1993
Special Collections, University of Virginia Law Library
MSS 93-3
This collection consists of 47 boxes.
The papers of Judge George H. Revercomb consist principally of the chambers files from his U.S. district judgeship, 1985-1993.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Biographical/Historical Information
George Hughes Revercomb was born in Charleston, West Virginia on June 3, 1929. Immediately after graduating from Princeton University with a B.A. in 1950, he started law school at the University of Virginia but left in 1951 to serve for two years as a lieutenant in the Air Force in Korea. Afterwards he returned to the University where he was member of the editorial board of the Virginia Law Review.
From the time of his law school graduation in 1955 until 1961, Revercomb practiced law in Roanoke at Hazlegrove, Shackelford & Carr, in Charleston, West Virginia at Revercomb & Price, and in Norfolk at Vanderventer, Black, Meredith and Martin. However, his law practice was interrupted by two years' work in Washington: from 1957 to 1958 in the law department of Southern Railroad, and from 1958 to 1959 at the Federal Communications Commission. By 1962 he was back in Washington practicing law, first by himself and afterwards as a partner at Reeves, Harrison, Sams and Revercomb. In 1960 he had married McCall Henderson, of Washington; they eventually made their home in McLean, Virginia.
In 1969 he joined the Justice Department as an associate deputy attorney general but left a year later when President Nixon appointed him to the newly formed Superior Court of the District of Columbia. In 1985 President Reagan appointed him to the U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia, the seat he held until his death from cancer in 1993.
Judge Revercomb was a visiting lecturer at the University of Virginia Law School for many years and was a member of the law school's first class (1982) of judges to receive the LL.M in the Judicial Process. Before he went on the bench he was active in the Republican party and participated in numerous state and national bar association activities. And in 1970 he was vice-chairman of the U.S. Delegation to the United Nations Conference on Prevention of Crime and Treatment of Offenders in Kyoto, Japan. He was a fellow of the American Bar Foundation and took an active role in the Judicial Counsel for the D. C. Circuit and the U. S. Judicial Conference.
Chief Justice William Rehnquist spoke at the dedication of the Revercomb portrait at the D.C. District Courthouse in May of 1994. He recalled his long friendship with the judge and the many evenings he and his wife spent playing bridge with McCall and George Revercomb. Of Revercomb's service on the court Rehnquist said:
For him, judging was a calling, just as the ministry is a calling for some. He had always wanted to be a judge. From the time he ascended the bench, as we judges like to put it, until his death last summer, he upheld the very best traditions of the Judiciary.
What could better illustrate this than his determination, in his final days in the hospital, to complete his decision in the complicated dispute arising out of the construction of the Green Line of the Metro system Mergentime Corporation v. Washington Metropolitan Area Transportation Authority, signed on July 30, two days before he died].
On the occasion of the dedication two former law clerks spoke of their great admiration and affection for the judge. In Theodore C. Whitehouse's words:
Each of us obtained from our service with Judge Revercomb an education about law, service, unwavering adherence to principle,and above all, a respect for the dignity of every person. We also gained an invaluable friend and mentor who was always there to advise and help whenever he could....
He never lost his intense concern for each litigant who appeared before him because to him, cases were about people, and he wanted to be very sure that the people affected by his decisions were treated fairly and justly. This was especially true where criminal sentencing was concerned....
Judge Revercomb fulfilled his life-long ambition to be a judge, and carried out that office with honor and distinction to the very end. (860 F. Supp. LXVII -LXXIV)
Scope and Content Information
The Papers of Judge George H. Revercomb (47 boxes, 20 linear feet) consist of the chambers files for his U.S. district judgeship. They are organized in four groups, maintaining the excellent order imposed in the judge's office. The papers bear witness to Revercomb's reputation as an efficient, hard-working, and well-organized judge.
About a quarter of the collection pertains to personal/professional and administrative matters. In addition to a small amount of personal correspondence, speeches, personnel files, and similar materials, there are log books and detailed calendars of cases, and newsclippings.
The preponderance of cases represented are civil and include the judge's last case, Mergentime Corporation v. Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority. This lengthy and complicated case involving construction of the District's Metro Green Line was one that Revercomb finished from his hospital bed; he signed the 250-page findings and opinion two days before his death. The majority of the criminal cases in this collection involve drugs. The best-known of them, U.S. v. Williams-Davis, or the R Street Case, was tried in 1991 and involved twenty-two defendants accused of racketeering, drug conspiracy, drug sales, as well as first-degree murder.
About 280 opinions for the civil cases found in this collection were published and ten opinions for the criminal cases. A database search indicates that about 50 of Revercomb's published cases are not represented in these files.
Organization
The papers are arranged in the following groups:
Administrative Files: personal correspondence, log books, calendars, jury instructions, etc. dating primarily 1985-93; also two notebooks of appellate slip opinions, dating from 1971-84, GHR's years on the D.C. Superior Court. Boxes 1-11
Civil Case Files: copies of selected court records for about 145 cases that were on the docket in the 1990s; at least 36 of these cases were decided before GHR's death, and his orders or opinions can be found in later boxes. Boxes 12-40
Decisions in Civil Cases: orders, opinions, a small amount of research material for about 410 cases; arranged alphabetically. Boxes 41-46
Decisions in Criminal Cases: opinions for 28 cases, arranged alphabetically. Box 46
Miscellany, including printed material, photographs, caricature of the judge, etc. Box 47
Contents List
- Administrative Files
  - Administrative Office of the U.S. Courts-Memoranda 1993 (Box 1)
  - ADR [Alternative Dispute Resolution] 1989-1992 (Box 1)
  - Appeals Files-Cases in which Judge Revercomb sat by Designation 1991, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Appeals Files-Judgement Orders 1985-1989, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Appeals Files-Judgement Orders 1988-1993, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Appeals Files-Notices of Appeals 1988-1993, 5 folders (Box 2)
  - Appeals Files-Slip Opinions in Judge's Cases 1985-1992, 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Appellate Slip Opinions Yearly File 1980, 1982, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Appellate Slip Opinions Permanent File 1971-1984, Black notebook (Box 3)
  - Appellate Slip Opinions Duplicate File 1971-1984, Black notebook (Box 3)
  - Calendar, Correspondence, Memoranda 1986-1993 (Box 4)
  - Court-related Correspondence 1986-1992, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Court-related Correspondence [civil management, includes GHR's handwritten description of his system] 1992 (Box 4)
  - Desk Calendar 1992-1993 (Box 4)
  - Early Evaluations 1989 (Box 4)
  - Eulogy by Judge F. Greene 1993 (Box 4)
  - Intern Applications. Restricted 1988-1993 (Box 4)
  - Investiture to U.S. District Court 1986 (Box 4)
  - Jury Instructions and Voir Dire Questions used by GHR 1985-1992, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Jury Verdict Forms n.d. (Box 5)
  - Law Clerks. Restricted 1974-1993, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Log Books-all active cases. [Recording dates of action] 1985-1993, 4 folders (Box 6)
  - Log Books-all active and closed cases. [Reocrding dates of action] 1985-1987, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Log Books-all active and closed cases. [Reocrding dates of action] 1988-1989, 4 folders (Box 7)
  - Log Books-all active and closed cases. [Reocrding dates of action] 1990-1991, 5 folders (Box 8)
  - Log Book-all active and closed cases. [Reocrding dates of action] 1992 (Box 9)
  - Log Book-Active Criminal Cases 1986-1992 (Box 9)
  - Mediation 1989, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous Papers 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Newspapers regarding GHR's cases 1970-1991, 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Personal Correspondence. [Copy of letter to Clarence Thomas re his nomination to the Supreme Court, June 1991 1985-1993 (Box 10)
  - "R" St. Crew Criminal Cases Log Book [Recording dates of action] 1991-1993 (Box 10)
  - "R" St. Crew Trial newsclippings 1992 (Box 10)
  - Report of the Judicial Conference Committee to Review the Criminal Justice Act 1993 (Box 10)
  - U.S. Judicial Conference. Committee on Defender Services 1993 (Box 10)
  - Speech Materials 1990-1991 (Box 10)
  - Statistical Reports-U.S. District Court 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - U.S. District Court Appointment-Letters of Commendation 1985-1986 (Box 11)
  - U.S. District Court Appointment Process-Supportive papers, questionnaires 1985 (Box 11)
- Civil Case Files
  - Amiercan Mopac International v. Cheney. 92-2317 1992, 5 folders (Box 12)
  - American Postal Workers Union, AFL-CIO v. Postal Service. 92-1942 1992 (Box 12)
  - Abdul-Hakim v. D.C. Department of Corrections. 92-0306 1992 (Box 13)
  - Anderson v. Holmes 92-0530 1992 (Box 13)
  - In re Aqunetta T. Anderson 92-0215 1992 (Box 13)
  - Banks v. Otis Elevator Co. 90-0200 [Negligence and personal injury] 1990-1991 (Box 13)
  - Barnes v. Maryland Cable Corp. 92-418 1992 (Box 13)
  - Boatwright v. Amivest Corp. 91-0284 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - Braxton v. D.C. Department of Corrections 92-0169 1992 (Box 13)
  - Breed v. Nansay Hawaii, Inc. 91-2837 1992, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Bressler v. Brintzer 91-3239 1992 (Box 14)
  - Brown v. Patrick 91-0068 [accident] 1991 (Box 14)
  - Cameron v. Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority [WMATA] 90-2875 1991 (Box 14)
  - Cash v. Henderson 91-1391 1992 (Box 14)
  - Cato v. Adams 91-2241 [job discrimination] 1991 (Box 14)
  - Claybrook v. Ridley 92-2281 [complaint for violation of civil rights] 1992 (Box 14)
  - Cleveland Clinic v. Sullivan 90-3048 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Cloisters West Homeowners Association v. Sullivan Corp. 88-2847 1990 (Box 15)
  - Cohen v. Department of the Air Force 89-359 1991 (Box 15)
  - Coleman v. Silber 92-2327 1992 (Box 15)
  - Connors v. Arch of Illinois, Inc. 86-1316 1990 (Box 15)
  - Connors v. Eastern Coal Co. 87-2492 1987-1991, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Connors v. Florence Mining Co. 92-1804 1992 (Box 16)
  - Connors v. Island Creek Coal Co. 86-0299 1986-1988, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Connors v. Island Creek Coal Co. and Consolidated Cases. 86-0299; 86-1316; 87-2495; 90-0257; 92-0479 1992, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Connors v. Meadow River Coal Co. 92-0479 1992 (Box 17)
  - Connors v. Middle Fork Corp. 89-0698 1989-1993, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Connors v. Tahoma Mining Co. 90-0257 1990 (Box 17)
  - Contract Freighters v. Travelers Indemnity 90-3050 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - In re Cooper 91-794 1992 (Box 18)
  - Copeland v. Morris 91-1150 1991 (Box 18)
  - Curtis v. Aluminum Association 91-1778 1991 (Box 18)
  - Dantzler v. U.S. 92-2737 [car accident] 1992-1993 (Box 18)
  - Darby v. Wood 91-685 [assault and battery] 1991, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Dejoie v. Sullivan 92-1635 [race discrimination] 1992 (Box 18)
  - Denjac Music Co. v. Signal Knob Radio Partners 91-2560 [copyright infringement] 1991 (Box 18)
  - Deter Co. v. Comer 92-2311 1992 (Box 18)
  - Developers Service Corp. v. American Mortgage Servicing Corp. 92-1769 1992 (Box 18)
  - District of Columbia v. A.A. Beiro Construction Co. 87-2171 1987-1990 (Box 18)
  - D.W.S. Holding v. Jackson 88-3652 1991 (Box 19)
  - EBM Group Corp. Ltd. v. Gulfstream Aerospace Corp. 92-1454 1992 (Box 19)
  - Edmond v. U.S. Postal Service. 88-0241 [reward] 1992 (Box 19)
  - Educational Training Concepts, Inc. v. Win International 89-1162 [breach of contract action] 1989-1990 (Box 19)
  - Ellis County, Texas v. U.S. 92-1110 [preclearance for redistricting plan] 1992 (Box 19)
  - Emory v. Psychiatric Institutes of America 89-2181 [job discrimination] 1989-1991, 4 folders (Box 19)
  - Emory v. Psychiatric Institutes of America 1989-1991, 4 folders (Box 20)
  - Executive Quarters, Inc. v. Hinckman 92-2115 1992 (Box 20)
  - Fazzini v. U.S. Department of Justice 91-1756 1991, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Federal Insurance Co V. Weinghast 90-1004 1990 (Box 21)
  - First American Bank v. Corby-Lynn Real Estate Co. 91-0356 1991 (Box 21)
  - Franklin Asaph Limited Partnership v. Federal Deposit Insurance Corp. 91-1856 1992, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Frye v. U.S. Environmental Protection Agency 90-3041 1991 (Box 21)
  - Golden v. General Services Administration 89-1009 1992 (Box 22)
  - Gorham v. D.C. Department of Corrections 92-2374 1992 (Box 2)
  - Gould v. Days Inn of America Franchising Inc. 92-0792 1992 (Box 22)
  - Graham v. Durham 91-381 [auto-negligence] 1991-1993, 3 folders (Box 22)
  - Gray v. Neoplan U.S. Corp. v. National Security Company 92-0849 1992 (Box 22)
  - Green v. Resolution Trust Corp. 92-1289 [complaint to recover deposits] 1992 (Box 22)
  - Group Hospitalization and Medical Services, Inc. v. Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority 91-2715. [Sub claim related to Silvas v. WMATA and D.C., 90-127] 1991 (Box 22)
  - Gulbrandson v. Commissioner of Patents and Trademarks 92-1587 1992, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Hanson v. Greenspan 91-1599 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Hayes v. District of Columbia 90-1972 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Hayes v. U.S. 92-2415 [violation of civil rights] 1992 (Box 24)
  - Henderson v. Inner City Settlements, Inc. 92-0145 1992 (Box 24)
  - Henderson v. Lujan 91-1356 1991 (Box 24)
  - Hill v. Hyatt Corp. 89-2931 1990-1991 (Box 24)
  - Holland v. CIA 91-1233 1985-1992, 4 folders (Box 24)
  - I.A.M. National Pension Fund v. Swayze Folding Box Co. 91-0090 1991 (Box 25)
  - IBM Corp. v. Federal Deposit Insurance Co. 92-1138 1992 (Box 25)
  - IBPATU [International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades Union & Industry Pension Fund] v. Brandon and Moreno Corp. 91-0566 1991 (Box 25)
  - IBPATU v. Claser Painting Corp. 91-0294 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - IBPATU v. Duo Signs 92-2762 1992-1993 (Box 25)
  - IBPATU v. Robinson 91-1699 1991 (Box 25)
  - Independent American Savings Association v. Banditree, Inc. 91-1256 1990-1991 (Box 25)
  - International Transcription Services, Inc. v. U.S. 90-3129 1990-1991 (Box 25)
  - ITPE MEBA/MNU Funds v. United International Investigate Services 90-0066 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Jackson v. Sullivan 92-1074 1992-1993 (Box 26)
  - Joyce v. Torsiello and Sons, Inc. 92-1036. [money damages] 1992 (Box 26)
  - 1700 Kalorama Corp. v. Federal Deposit Insurance Corp. 91-1886 1991 (Box 26)
  - Kenney v. Roland Parson Contracting Corp. 91-1230 1991, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Kenney v. Lott Constructors, Inc. 91-3187 1992 (Box 26)
  - In re Knox Trading and Development Co. 91-0831 1992 (Box 26)
  - Lawyers Title Insurance Corp. v. Dolphin Evans Settlements, Inc. 91-1398 1991-1993, 3 folders (Box 27)
  - Lee v. D'Alessandro 92-1505 1992, 3 folders (Box 27)
  - Lee v. Baker 92-1538 1992 (Box 28)
  - Lee v. Brady 87-0977 1993 (Box 28)
  - Lee v. Daly 92-1537 1992 (Box 28)
  - Lee v. Stickney 92-1632 1992, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Leeds v. Quigg 89-0635 1991 (Box 28)
  - Lewis v. WMATA 90-0678 [negligence-personal injury] 1989 (Box 28)
  - Lifschultz Fast Freight, Inc. v. Union Hardware, Inc. 91-2538 1991 (Box 28)
  - Lindholm v. U.S. 92-2136 1992, 1 folder (Box 28)
  - Lindholm v. U.S. 92-2136 1992, 8 folders (Box 29-30)
  - MacPherson v. Searle Co. 90-0095 1990-1992, 6 folders (Box 31)
  - Major v. First Federal Savings Arkansas 90-2450 1990 (Box 32)
  - Mason v. Ridley 92-2267 [Petition Writ for Habeas Corpus] 1992 (Box 32)
  - Massquoi v. Immigration & Naturalization Service 92-2031 1992-1993 (Box 32)
  - McClelland v. U.S. Postal Service 92-1026 1992 (Box 32)
  - McCormack v. Mozie & Potomac Electric Co. 92-2698 [car accident] 1992 (Box 32)
  - McDowell v. Allstate Insurance Co., Inc. 91-434 1991 (Box 32)
  - Re Marlene and James F. McGuirl 90-2073 [bankruptcy] 1990 (Box 32)
  - McCullogh v. McPherson 90-2365 [car accident] 1991 (Box 32)
  - Mendivil v. Barr. 91-3273 [discrimination] 1992 (Box 32)
  - Michael's Piano, Inc. v. Federal Trade Commission 92-1267 [Freedom of Information Act] 1992 (Box 32)
  - Neill v. Department of Justice 91-3319 1991, 3 folders (Box 32)
  - Ogle v. Southland Co. 92-2222 [Americans with Disabilities Act] 1992 (Box 33)
  - Olaleye v. Barr 92-1608 1992 (Box 33)
  - Pennant v. PSI, Inc. 92-2782 [discrimination] 1992-1993 (Box 33)
  - Perkins v. Prince George County Government 92-0861 [conspiracy to violate civil rights] 1992 (Box 33)
  - Place v. Nicholson 91-2085 [diversity-auto negligence] 1991 (Box 33)
  - Reback v. Parsons 90-0348 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 33)
  - Reback v. Parsons 90-0348 1990-1991, 4 folders (Box 34)
  - Resolution Trust Corp. v. H.D.G., Inc. 91-1485 1991 (Box 34)
  - Reeve Aleutian Airways v. U.S. 88-0897 1991 (Box 35)
  - Roberst v. D.C. Department of Corrections & Teamsters Local Union. 91-3030 [job discrimination] 1989-1992, 4 folders (Box 35)
  - Robinson v. Garrett 88-2903 [gender-based discrimination] 1991 (Box 36)
  - Robinson v. Mount Vernon Realty, Inc. 86-0931 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Resolution Trust Corporation [RTC] v. Banco Santander Puerto Rico 92-367 1992 (Box 36)
  - RTC as Conservator of Trustbank Federal Savings Banks v. Bildman 91-632 1991, 1 folder (Box 36)
  - RTC as Conservator of Trustbank Federal Savings Bank v. Bildman 91-632 1991, 1 folder (Box 37)
  - RTC v. Gibson 90-112 1992, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Service Employees International Union & Welfare Fund v. Douglas 91-0320 1991 (Box 37)
  - Shields v. Jackson 92-1711 1992-1993 (Box 37)
  - Shields v. Washington State Human Rights Commission 92-1703 1992 (Box 37)
  - Simmons v. Hawkins 91-2471, -2472, -2474, -2475, -2476 1991 (Box 37)
  - Simmons v. D.C. Department of Corrections 92-2379 [violation of human rights] 1992 (Box 37)
  - Smith v. Evans 91-0975 [violation of constitutional rights] 1991-1992 (Box 37)
  - Smith v. Garrett 91-1809 [racial discrimination] 1991 (Box 37)
  - Southern Technologies v. U.S. 90-1868 1990, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - Southland Corp. v. Godette 91-CV-0999 1991, 4 folders (Box 39)
  - Starner v. Michigan Ladder 91-3095 [products liability action] 1991 (Box 39)
  - Sutton v. U.S. 91-0461 [violation of due process] 1991 (Box 39)
  - Taylor v. Ridley 92-2545 [habeas corpus] 1992 (Box 39)
  - Thompson v. U.S. 90-1658 [complaint for damages] 1990 (Box 39)
  - U.S., for the use of Marmet Corp. v. Becon Services Corp. 91-2502 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 40)
  - U.S. v. Caribbean Basin Development Corp. 92-1747 1992 (Box 40)
  - U.S. v. Clawson 89-0321 [violation of highway safety] 1991 (Box 40)
  - U.S. v. Mathews 91-0568 1991 (Box 40)
  - U.S. v. Property identified as $10, 111.34...91-2045 1993 (Box 40)
  - U.S. v. Property identified as 5201 Kansas Ave., N.W. Washington, D.C. 91-2073 1991 (Box 40)
  - U.S. v. Sandridge 87-2386 1991 (Box 40)
  - Valley Supply & Equipment Co. v. Mergentine Corp. 90-2478 1990-1991 (Box 40)
  - Walker v. Dixon 91-1460 [excessive force used for arrest] 1991-1992 (Box 40)
  - Wardman Realty and Construction Co. v. Federal Deposit Insurance Corp. 91-1885 [monetary damages] 1991 (Box 40)
  - Washington Hospital Center Corp. v. Waters and Waters v. U.S. Operating the Civil Health and Medical Program of the Uniformed Services 91-1638 1991, 1 folder (Box 40)
  - Washington Hospital Corp. v. Waters 91-1638 1991, 1 folder (Box 41)
  - Weather Data Services, Inc. v. U.S. Department of Commerce 92-1740 1992 (Box 41)
- Civil Cases-Opinions, Orders, Etc.
  - ABB Flakt, Inc. v. A/S Niro, 91-1429 (Box 41)
  - Abramson v. Frank 89-1892 (Box 41)
  - Adams v. Dyna Span Corp. 88-0484 (Box 41)
  - Ago v. Begg, Inc. 85-2229 (Box 41)
  - Allen v. U.S. Capitol Police 90-2084 (Box 41)
  - Avins v. Cavazos 89-2057 (Box 41)
  - Alley v. Resolution Trust Corp. 91-0220 (Box 41)
  - Alvarado Parkway Institute v. Mendez 90-0490 (Box 41)
  - American Federation of Government Employees v. Calhoun 87-1806 (Box 41)
  - American Library Association v. Thornburgh 89-0661 (Box 41)
  - American Mopac International v. Cheney 92-2317 (Box 41)
  - American Security Bank v. York 91-1212 (Box 41)
  - Anchorena v. District of Columbia 87-2942 (Box 41)
  - Anderson v. District of Columbia 90-0464 (Box 41)
  - Anderson v. Niklas 92-1215 (Box 41)
  - Archuleta v. Sullivan 89-1366 (Box 41)
  - Assassination Archives and Research Center v. CIA 88-2600 (Box 41)
  - Association of Business Publishers v. US Postal Service 88-829 (Box 41)
  - Association of National Health Service Corp. Scholarship Recipients v. Bowen 86-2925 (Box 41)
  - Averbach v. Sverdup Corp. 85-2493 (Box 41)
  - Automated Services, Inc. v. Department of Justice 86-0497 (Box 41)
  - Avins v. Cavazos 89-2057 (Box 41)
  - Baird v. Paredes 88-1074 (Box 41)
  - Baker v. Meese 87-530 (Box 41)
  - Bank St. Croix v. Federal Deposit Insurance 90-2924 (Box 41)
  - Banks v. District of Columbia 88-1363 (Box 41)
  - Banner v. U.S. Department of Commerce 86-1117 (Box 41)
  - Barksdale v. Washington Terminal Co. 87-1072 (Box 41)
  - Beale v. District of Columbia 91-0262 (Box 41)
  - Bell v. Colonial Parking, Inc. 91-0592 (Box 41)
  - Berger v. Safeway Stores 91-0480 (Box 41)
  - Berlacher v. Painewebber, Inc. 90-2188 (Box 41)
  - Berton v. Plaut 86-1701 (Box 41)
  - Bias v. Advantage International 87-1995 (Box 41)
  - Bigelow v. Knight 89-1542 (Box 41)
  - Black v. Braxton 88-1052 (Box 41)
  - Black v. Turnage 86-2187 (Box 41)
  - Block v. Pitney Bowes, Inc. 87-2618 (Box 41)
  - Boggins v. Quilan 88-2796 (Box 41)
  - Bowman v. T. Rowe Price Associates 86-2208 (Box 41)
  - Bradley v. Melrose Co. 90-1676 (Box 41)
  - Braxton v. U.S. Parole Commission 87-3339 (Box 41)
  - Bridges v. Williams 89-1648 (Box 41)
  - Brown v. Barr 92-2416 (Box 41)
  - Brown v. Barry 88-0565 (Box 41)
  - Brown v. U.S. 89-1676 (Box 41)
  - Building and Construction Trades Dept. v. Reich 91-2731 (Box 41)
  - Burgess v. Sullivan 89-2731 (Box 41)
  - Burress v. Hilton Hotels Corp. 88-0623 (Box 41)
  - Bush v. Charles Smith Co. 90-2963 (Box 41)
  - Bush v. WMATA 87-1394 (Box 41)
  - Cain v. Bradco Supply Co. 88-0967 (Box 41)
  - Caldwell v. Quinlan 88-0292 (Box 41)
  - Calvin Klein Industries v. Lawrence & Athanasios 89-0357 (Box 41)
  - Carolina v. Kaiser Foundation 89-0850 (Box 41)
  - Castorr v. Paine Webber Jackson & Curtis, Inc. 85-1455 (Box 41)
  - Chacon v. D.E.A. 90-2854 (Box 41)
  - Charles A. v. Meese 85-3767 (Box 41)
  - Clark v. Harp 89-3469 (Box 41)
  - Cleveland Clinic Foundation v. Sullivan 90-3048 (Box 41)
  - Clift v. Clift 88-3563 (Box 41)
  - Clipper v. Frank 88-2463 (Box 41)
  - Coast Federal Savings Bank v. Director, Office of Thrift Supervision 91-0349 (Box 41)
  - Coates v. D.C. 88-2608 (Box 41)
  - Coates v. WMATA 90-0679 (Box 41)
  - Colonial Trading Corp. v. Dept. of the Navy 87-1406 (Box 42)
  - Cohen v. U.S. Dept. of the Air Force 89-0359 (Box 42)
  - Colonial Penn Insurance Co. v. Owens 88-3670 (Box 42)
  - Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador v. Sessions 88-3430 (Box 42)